택시 창밖으로 번지는 불빛
The lights blurring outside the taxi window
라디오에서 흘러나온 옛날 노래
An old song playing on the radio
이 시간엔 모든 게 느려져
At this hour, everything slows down
너한테 갈까 말까 고민만 해
I just keep wondering if I should go to you
편의점 앞 벤치에 앉아서
Sitting on the bench in front of the convenience store
따뜻한 캔 하나 손에 쥐고
Holding a warm can in my hand
네 연락을 기다리는 건 아닌데
It's not that I'm waiting for your call, but
자꾸 화면을 확인하게 돼
I keep checking my screen
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
A 2 AM night when the frequency is right
잡음 사이로 네 목소리가 들려
I hear your voice through the static
이 도시가 잠들면 우리만 깨어서
When this city falls asleep, only we are awake
같은 하늘 아래 다른 곳에서
Under the same sky, in different places
옥상에서 내려다본 골목길
The alleyway I look down on from the rooftop
가로등 하나가 깜빡이고 있어
A streetlamp is flickering
하고 싶은 말은 루프처럼 돌아
The words I want to say spin like a loop
입 밖으론 한마디도 못 꺼내
I can't utter a single word
이어폰 한쪽만 끼고 걸어
I walk with only one earphone in
네가 좋아하던 그 노래 틀어
I play that song you liked
발걸음이 리듬을 타는 밤
A night where my steps follow the rhythm
혼자인데 혼자가 아닌 것 같아
I'm alone, but it doesn't feel like I'm alone
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
A 2 AM night when the frequency is right
잡음 사이로 네 목소리가 들려
I hear your voice through the static
이 도시가 잠들면 우리만 깨어서
When this city falls asleep, only we are awake
같은 하늘 아래 다른 곳에서
Under the same sky, in different places
전화할까 말까 세 번째 고민
It's the third time I'm wondering whether to call or not
나도 지금 네 번호 보고 있어
I'm looking at your number right now too
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
A 2 AM night when the frequency is right
잡음 속에서 결국 너를 찾아
Finally, I find you through the static
이 도시가 잠들어도 우리는 깨어서
Even if this city sleeps, we are awake
같은 주파수로 이어져 있어
We are connected by the same frequency